Guide to the King County Nurses Association Records
Special Collections, University of Washington Libraries
- King County Nurses Association records, 1959-1989; 3049-004; 9.12 cubic feet 8 boxes and 1 Vertical File
  SERIES 1: CORRESPONDENCE AND MEETING MINUTES, 1980-1989
  SERIES 2: CONVENTIONS, 1974-1985
  Subseries A: Washington State Nurses’ Association Convention, 1974-1985
  Subseries B: American Nurses' Association Convention, 1975-1985
  SERIES 3: FINANCIAL RECORDS, 1977-1980
  SERIES 4: COMMITTEE ANNUAL REPORTS, 1980-1982
  SERIES 5: NEWSLETTERS AND PUBLISHED MATERIAL, 1978-1986
  SERIES 6: EVENT PARTICIPATION, 1979-1986
  SERIES 7: COMMUNICATIONS/POLITICAL AWARENESS SUBJECT FILES, 1979-1987
  SERIES 8: MEMBERSHIP FILES, 1984-1988
  SERIES 9: CONTINUING EDUCATION RECOGNITION PROGRAM, 1982-1986
  SERIES 10: SPECIAL INTEREST GROUPS, 1965-1986
  SUBGROUP 2: BOARD OF DIRECTORS, 1959-1986
  SERIES 1: BOARD ORIENTATION MATERIALS, 1959-1985
  SERIES 2: MEETING MOTIONS, 1973-1986
  SERIES 3: MEETING AGENDAS AND MINUTES, 1978-1985
  SUBGROUP 3: BYLAWS COMMITTEE, 1972-1987
  SUBGROUP 4: COMMITTEE ON COMMITTEES, 1967-1986
  SUBGROUP 5: COMMUNICATION/POLITICAL AWARENESS SUBCOMMITTEE, 1975-1985
  SUBGROUP 6: ETHNIC MINORITY AFFAIRS COMMITTEE, 1982-1986
  SUBGROUP 7: EXCELLENCE IN NURSING PRACTICE AWARDS COMMITTEE, 1979-1986
  SUBGROUP 8: FINANCE COMMITTEE, 1974-1987
  SUBGROUP 9: MEMBERSHIP COMMITTEE, 1972-1987
  SUBGROUP 10: NOMINATION COMMITTEE, 1977-1987
  SUBGROUP 11: NURSE OF THE YEAR AWARD COMMITTEE, 1978-1985
  SUBGROUP 12: NURSE PRACTICE COMMITTEE, 1973-1987
  SUB-SUBGROUP A: SCHOOL HEALTH SUBCOMMITTEE, 1976-1987
  SUBGROUP 13: PROGRAM COMMITTEE, 1972-1986
  SUB-SUBGROUP A: ALL DAY EVENT TASK FORCE, 1984-1986
  SUBGROUP 14: PUBLIC RELATIONS COMMITTEE, 1979-1986
  SUB-SUBGROUP A: SPECIAL PUBLIC RELATIONS TASK FORCE, 1980-1984
  SUBGROUP 15: INTERORGANIZATIONAL INVOLVEMENT, 1975-1986
  SUB-SUBGROUP A: KING COUNTY NURSES ASSOCIATION/KING COUNTY MEDICAL SOCIETY INTERPROFESSIONAL COMMITTEE, 1975-1986
  SUB-SUBGROUP B: HOME HEALTH SERVICES OF PUGET SOUND ADVISORY COMMITTEE, 1979-1981
  SUB-SUBGROUP C: NATIONAL HEALTH SERVICES CORPS JAIL HEALTH ADVISORY COMMITTEE, 1979-1985
  Donated by the Association, 8/2/1989.
  - KING COUNTY NURSES ASSOCIATION OFFICE FILES, 1965-1989; 1974-1989; SUBGROUP 1 (Box-folder 1/1-3/26, 8/16)
    - Handbook and Guidelines, 1967-1984 (Box-folder 1/1)
    - Executive Director Job Search Materials, 1979 (Box-folder 1/2)
    - Committee Meeting Attendance Sign-Up Sheets, 1982 (Box-folder 1/3)
    - Committee Meeting Attendance Sign-Up Sheets, 1983 (Box-folder 1/4)
    - CORRESPONDENCE AND MEETING MINUTES, 1980-1989; SERIES 1 (Box-folder 1/5-29, 8/16)
      Contains primarily correspondence to and from the Executive Director, Alma Ware, board members, and committee chairs on assorted topics, including events, thank you letters, membership, and committee business. A number of the folders consist of weekly mailing packets sent to KCNA President Ginny Kenyon with general correspondence as well as meeting minutes and agendas of the various committees.
      - Office Space Lease, 1980 (Box-folder 1/5)
      - Early Periodic Screening Diagnosis Treatment (EPSDT) Project, 1980 (Box-folder 1/6)
      - Katherine Bradley's Master's Thesis Questionnaire, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 1/7)
      - General Correspondence, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 1/8)
      - General Correspondence (1 of 2), 1982-1983 (Box-folder 1/9)
      - General Correspondence (2 of 2), 1982-1983 (Box-folder 1/10)
      - District and Committee Meeting Correspondence and Minutes, 1983 (Box-folder 1/11)
      - General and Committee Correspondence, 1983 (Box-folder 1/12)
      - Staff and Committee Meeting Minutes and General Correspondence, 1983 (Box-folder 1/13)
      - General Correspondence to and from King County Nurses Association Board and Chairs, 1983 (Box-folder 1/14)
      - General Correspondence and Committee and Staff Meeting Minutes, 1983 April-June (Box-folder 1/15)
      - General Correspondence and Committee Meeting Minutes, 1983 October (Box-folder 1/16)
      - General Correspondence and Committee Meeting Minutes, 1983 May-July (Box-folder 1/17)
      - General Correspondence and Committee Meeting Minutes, 1984 January (Box-folder 1/18)
      - General and Committee Correspondence and Meeting Minutes, 1984 January-March (Box-folder 1/19)
      - General Correspondence and Committee Meeting Minutes, 1984 March-April (Box-folder 1/20)
      - General and Committee Correspondence and Meeting Minutes, 1984 April-September (Box-folder 1/21)
      - Committee General Correspondence and Meeting Minutes, 1984 (Box-folder 1/22)
      - General and Committee Correspondence and Meeting Minutes, 1984 (Box-folder 1/23)
      - Meeting Correspondence and Minutes, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 1/24)
      - General Correspondence (1 of 2), 1984-1987 (Box-folder 1/25)
      - General Correspondence (2 of 2), 1984-1987 (Box-folder 1/26)
      - Reference Letters for KCNA Members, 1985-1987 (Box-folder 8/16)
      - President's Circulating File: Correspondence and Committee/Task Force Minutes, 1987 (Box-folder 1/27)
      - President's Circulating File: Correspondence and Committee/Task Force Minutes (1 of 2), 1988-1989 (Box-folder 1/28)
      - President's Circulating File: Correspondence and Committee/Task Force Minutes (2 of 2), 1988-1989 (Box-folder 1/29)
    - CONVENTIONS, 1974-1985; SERIES 2 (Box-folder 1/30-31, 2/1-13)
      - Washington State Nurses' Association Convention, 1974-1985; Subseries A (Box-folder 1/30-31, 2/1-5)
        - King County Nurses Association Hostess Committee Materials, 1974, 1977-1978 (Box-folder 1/30)
        - Convention Delegates, 1977-1978 (Box-folder 1/31)
        - Convention Materials, 1978 (Box-folder 1/32)
        - Convention Materials, 1979 (Box-folder 2/1)
        - Board of Directors Washington State Nurses Association Convention Task Force, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 2/2)
          Contains photograph of unidentified awards recipient.
        - Convention Materials, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 2/3)
        - Convention Materials, 1982-1984 (Box-folder 2/4)
        - Convention Materials, 1985 (Box-folder 2/5)
      - American Nurses' Association Convention, 1975-1985; Subseries B (Box-folder 2/6-13)
        - Convention Materials and Nomination Applications, 1975-1978 (Box-folder 2/6)
        - Convention Materials and House Of Delegates Summary of Action, 1980 (Box-folder 2/7)
        - Convention Materials (1 of 2), 1982 (Box-folder 2/8)
          Includes issue of American Nurses Association Convention News
        - Convention Materials (2 of 2), 1982 (Box-folder 2/9)
        - Convention Materials: Year of Structure Change, 1982 (Box-folder 2/10)
        - Group Travel Materials (China, Hawaii, San Jose - American Travel Co, Jim Smith), 1982 (Box-folder 2/11)
        - 1984 Convention Materials, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 2/12)
        - House Of Delegates Registration, 1985 (Box-folder 2/13)
    - FINANCIAL RECORDS, 1977-1980; SERIES 3 (Box-folder 2/14-27)
      - Consultants Contracts And Materials (Charge Budget Item 08-810), 1977-1980 (Box-folder 2/14)
      - Employee Insurance Materials (Charge Budget Item 11-810), 1979-1980 (Box-folder 2/15)
      - Subscriptions (Charge Budget Item 01-810), 1978-1980 (Box-folder 2/16)
      - Program Committee (Charge Budget Item 04-820), 1978-1980 (Box-folder 2/17)
      - Public Relations Committee (Charge Budget Item 05-820), 1977-1980 (Box-folder 2/18)
      - Nurse Practice Committee Expenses (Charge Budget Item 08-820), 1978-1980 (Box-folder 2/19)
      - Nominating Committee (Charge Budget Item 09-820), 1978-1980 (Box-folder 2/20)
      - Finance Committee (Charge Budget Item 10-820), 1979-1980 (Box-folder 2/21)
      - Membership Committee (Charge Budget Item 02-820), 1978-1980 (Box-folder 2/22)
      - Special Interest Groups (Charge Budget Item 00-830), 1978-1980 (Box-folder 2/23)
      - Gerontology (Charge Budget Item 04-830), 1979 (Box-folder 2/24)
      - Family Nurse Practitioners Correspondence (Charge Budget Item 06-830), 1979 (Box-folder 2/25)
      - Chart of Accounts, 1977 (Box-folder 2/26)
      - Dues Income (Charge Budget Item 501), 1979-1980 (Box-folder 2/27)
    - COMMITTEE ANNUAL REPORTS, 1980-1982; SERIES 4 (Box-folder 2/28-29)
      - District Annual Committee Reports, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 2/28)
      - District Annual Committee Reports, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 2/29)
    - NEWSLETTERS AND PUBLISHED MATERIAL, 1978-1986; SERIES 5 (Box-folder 2/30-35)
      - Washington State Nurses Association Newsletters, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 2/30)
      - Washington State Nurses Association Newsletters, 1982-1986 (Box-folder 2/31)
      - Washington State Nurses Association Legislative Bulletin, 1971 March-April (Box-folder 2/32)
      - Assorted Nursing Association Brochures, 1978-1984 (Box-folder 2/33)
      - King County Proclamation of Nursing Recognition Month, 1984 April (Box-folder 2/34)
      - "Advocate II" Newsletter, Volume 1, Number 2, 1979 October (Box-folder 2/35)
    - EVENT PARTICIPATION, 1979-1986; SERIES 6 (Box-folder 2/36-41)
      - Young Men's Christian Association (YMCA) City Fair Exhibit and Screenings (1 of 2), 1981 (Box-folder 2/36)
      - Young Men's Christian Association (YMCA) City Fair Exhibit and Screenings (2 of 2), 1981 (Box-folder 2/37)
      - Health Check Northwest Health Screenings (1 of 2), 1986 (Box-folder 2/38)
      - Health Check Northwest Health Screenings (2 of 2), 1986 (Box-folder 2/39)
      - Puget Sound Health Fair, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 2/40)
      - International Council of Nurses 1981 Sister Cities Task Force, 1979-1981 (Box-folder 2/41)
      - King County Nurses Association Show Me Health Fair Event Poster, 1985 (Vf:oversize OSVF0201)
    - COMMUNICATIONS/POLITICAL AWARENESS SUBJECT FILES, 1979-1987; SERIES 7 (Box-folder 2/42-3/1)
      - Seattle Department of Community Development Day Care Task Force, 1980-1982 (Box-folder 2/42)
      - Bicycle Safety, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 2/43)
      - Washington State Board of Nursing: Minutes, Regulation Amendments, Correspondence, 1979, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 2/44)
      - Washington State Board of Nursing: Minutes, Regulation Amendments, Correspondence, 1983-1985 (Box-folder 2/45)
      - Washington State Board of Nursing: Minutes, Regulation Amendments, Correspondence, 1979-1982 (Box-folder 2/46)
      - "A Marketing Research Study: Feasibility of Expanding an Adult Based Flexible Baccalaureate Program in Nursing at Seattle University" paper, 1987 (Box-folder 3/1)
    - MEMBERSHIP FILES, 1984-1988; SERIES 8 (Box-folder 3/2-5)
      - King County Nurses Association Newsletter Subscription Form, 1984-1986 (Box-folder 3/2)
      - Member Consent Forms, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 3/3)
      - Member Sign up Sheets, 1986 (Box-folder 3/4)
      - Member Sign up Sheets and Attendance Records, 1987 (Box-folder 3/5)
    - CONTINUING EDUCATION RECOGNITION PROGRAM, 1982-1986; SERIES 9 (Box-folder 3/6-12)
      Contains worksheets completed by members registered in continuing education courses on a variety of nursing, health, and other topics to assess the quality of the workshops and comprehension of those enrolled.
      - Educational Program Evaluations, 1986 (Box-folder 3/6)
      - Continuing Education Recognition Program (CERP) Approved Forms and Attendance Records (1 of 3), 1982 (Box-folder 3/7)
      - Continuing Education Recognition Program (CERP) Approved Forms and Attendance Records (2 of 3), 1982 (Box-folder 3/8)
      - Continuing Education Recognition Program (CERP) Approved Forms and Attendance Records (3 of 3), 1982 (Box-folder 3/9)
      - Continuing Education Recognition Program (CERP) Approved Forms and Attendance Records (1 of 3), 1983 (Box-folder 3/10)
      - Continuing Education Recognition Program (CERP) Approved Forms and Attendance Records (2 of 3), 1983 (Box-folder 3/11)
      - Continuing Education Recognition Program (CERP) Approved Forms and Attendance Records (3 of 3), 1983 (Box-folder 3/12)
    - SPECIAL INTEREST GROUPS, 1965-1986; SERIES 10 (Box-folder 3/13-3/26)
      Contains correspondence, meeting minutes, program evaluations, and other records from assorted special interest groups formed by the KCNA to investigate specific topics related to nursing, including gerontology, management, nurse educators, oncology, and primary health care.
      - Disciplinary Guidelines, 1981 (Box-folder 3/13)
      - Gerontology Special Interest Group Meeting Minutes, 1965-1986 (Box-folder 3/14)
      - Gerontology Correspondence, 1972-1986 (Box-folder 3/15)
      - Middle Management Special Interest Group Meeting Correspondence, 1977-1986 (Box-folder 3/16)
      - Middle Management Special Interest Group Meeting Agenda, 1977-1986 (Box-folder 3/17)
      - Middle Management Special Interest Group Program Evaluation, 1979-1986 (Box-folder 3/18)
      - Middle Management Steering Committee Correspondence, 1982 (Box-folder 3/19)
      - Nurse Educators Special Interest Group Correspondence, 1984-1986 (Box-folder 3/20)
      - Nurse Educators Special Interest Group Meeting Agenda, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 3/21)
      - Nurse Entrepreneur Special Interest Group Meeting Agendas, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 3/22)
      - Oncology Special Interest Group Correspondence, 1974-1984 (Box-folder 3/23)
      - Primary Health Care Nurse Practitioners Special Interest Group Correspondence, 1974-1985 (Box-folder 3/24)
      - Primary Health Care Nurse Practitioners Special Interest Group Agendas, 1973-1986 (Box-folder 3/25)
      - Staff Development Special Interest Group Correspondence and Materials, 1981-1986 (Box-folder 3/26)
  - BOARD OF DIRECTORS, 1959-1986; SUBGROUP 2 (Box-folder 3/27-5/4)
    Contains records of KCNA elected board members, including board orientation materials for new officers and records of board meetings, including motions documenting major decisions made, agendas, minutes, and other supporting materials.
    - BOARD ORIENTATION MATERIALS, 1959-1985; SERIES 1 (Box-folder 3/27-4/1)
      - Board Orientation Notebook Contents, 1978-1979 (Box-folder 3/27)
      - Board Orientation Materials, 1979-1981 (Box-folder 3/28)
      - Board of Directors Meeting - June Orientation, 1984 (Box-folder 3/29)
      - Board of Directors and Structural Unit Chairs Retreat Planning and Evaluations, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 3/30)
      - Board of Directors Rosters, 1976-1983 (Box-folder 3/31)
      - Policies Established by the Board of Directors, 1959-1969 (Box-folder 4/1)
    - MEETING MOTIONS, 1973-1986; SERIES 2 (Box-folder 4/2-11)
    - MEETINGS AGENDAS AND MINUTES, 1978-1985; SERIES 3 (Box-folder 4/12-5/4)
      - Board of Directors Executive Committee Meeting Minutes, 1978-1979 (Box-folder 5/4)
      - Meeting Agendas and Minutes, 1979 (Box-folder 4/12)
      - Washington State Nurses Association Board of Directors Meeting Agenda, 1979 November (Box-folder 4/13)
      - Meeting Agendas and Minutes, 1980 (Box-folder 4/14)
      - 2/6/80 Meeting Minutes and Materials, 1979 November-1980 February (Box-folder 4/15)
      - Meeting Minutes and Materials, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 4/16)
      - 04/1980 Meeting Minutes and Materials, 1980 January-June (Box-folder 4/17)
      - 4/26/80 Meeting Minutes and Materials, 1980 January-April (Box-folder 4/18)
      - 5/21/80 Meeting Minutes and Materials, 1980 April-May (Box-folder 4/19)
      - 9/27/80 Meeting Minutes and Materials, 1980 July-October (Box-folder 4/20)
      - 11/22/80 Meeting Minutes and Materials, 1980 September-December (Box-folder 4/21)
      - 2/19/81 Meeting Minutes and Materials, 1980 December-1981 April (Box-folder 4/22)
      - Meeting Agendas and Minutes, 1981 (Box-folder 4/23)
      - 4/16/81 Meeting Minutes and Materials, 1981 February-April (Box-folder 4/24)
      - 4/30/81 Special Board Meeting Minutes, 1981 April (Box-folder 4/25)
      - 5/16/81 Meeting Minutes and Materials, 1981 April-May (Box-folder 4/26)
      - 9/19/81 Meeting Minutes and Materials, 1981 March-October (Box-folder 4/27)
      - 11/13/81 Meeting Minutes and Materials, 1981 October-December (Box-folder 4/28)
      - Meeting Minutes and Updates, 1982 (Box-folder 4/29)
      - 1/23/82 Meeting Minutes and Materials, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 4/30)
      - 4/2/82 Meeting Minutes and Materials, 1982 February-April (Box-folder 4/31)
      - 6/11-6/12/82 Meeting Minutes and Materials, 1982 May-August (Box-folder 4/32)
      - 9/25/82 Meeting Minutes and Materials, 1982 August-October (Box-folder 4/33)
      - 11/12/82 Meeting Minutes and Materials, 1982 October-November (Box-folder 4/34)
      - Meeting Correspondence, Agendas, and Minutes, 1983 (Box-folder 4/35)
      - 1/29/83 Meeting Minutes and Materials, 1983 January-February (Box-folder 4/36)
      - 4/19/83 Special Meeting Minutes, 1983 April (Box-folder 4/37)
      - 4/30/83 Meeting Minutes and Materials, 1983 March-May (Box-folder 4/38)
      - 6/9-6/10/83 Meeting Minutes and Materials, 1983 May-June (Box-folder 4/39)
      - 8/31/83 Meeting Minutes and Materials, 1983 (Box-folder 4/40)
      - 11/12/83 Meeting Minutes and Materials, 1983 November-December (Box-folder 4/41)
      - Meeting Minutes and Agendas, 1984 (Box-folder 4/42)
      - 1/31/84 Meeting Minutes and Materials, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 4/43)
      - 3/17/84 Meeting Minutes and Materials, 1984 January-April (Box-folder 4/44)
      - 5/9/84 Meeting Minutes and Materials, 1984 March-June (Box-folder 4/45)
      - 6/7-6/8/84 Meeting Minutes and Materials, 1984 May-September (Box-folder 4/46)
      - 9/24/84 Meeting Minutes and Materials, 1984 April-September (Box-folder 4/47)
      - 11/27/84 Meeting Minutes and Materials, 1984 September-December (Box-folder 4/48)
      - 1/15/85 Structural Units and Board of Directors Meeting, 1985 January (Box-folder 4/49)
      - 1/26/85 Meeting Minutes and Materials, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 4/50)
      - 2/26/85 Meeting Minutes and Materials, 1985 (Box-folder 4/51)
      - 5/10/85 Meeting Minutes and Materials, 1985 (Box-folder 4/52)
      - 6/14/85 Meeting Minutes and Materials, 1985 (Box-folder 5/1)
      - 12/5/85 Meeting Minutes and Materials, 1985 September-December (Box-folder 5/2)
      - 9/28/85 Meeting Minutes and Materials, 1985 (Box-folder 5/3)
  - BYLAWS COMMITTEE, 1972-1987; SUBGROUP 3 (Box-folder 5/5-8, 8/17-18)
    Contains meeting minutes and revisions to the KCNA bylaws and Articles of Incorporation.
    - Bylaws Committee Meeting Minutes, 1979-1986 (Box-folder 5/5)
    - Bylaws Revisions and Explanations [1 of 2], 1979-1987 (Box-folder 8/17)
    - Bylaws Revisions and Explanations [2 of 2], 1979-1987 (Box-folder 8/18)
    - Bylaws Committee Membership, 1972-1976 (Box-folder 5/6)
    - Committee Review of American Nurses Association Bylaws Changes, 1974-1976 (Box-folder 5/7)
    - King County Nurses Association Articles of Incorporation Revisions, 1975 (Box-folder 5/8)
  - COMMITTEE ON COMMITTEES, 1967-1986; SUBGROUP 4 (Box-folder 5/9-14)
    Contains records related to the coordination of different KCNA committees, including the onboarding of new committee chairs and committee chair reports as well as committee member lists.
    - King County Nurses Association Handbook for Committee Chairmen, 1975 (Box-folder 5/9)
    - Committee Chairman Responsibilities, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 5/10)
    - Committee on Committees Minutes, 1974-1986 (Box-folder 5/11)
    - Committee Rosters, 1967-1984 (Box-folder 5/12)
    - Chairperson's Report to Committee on Committees, 1979 (Box-folder 5/13)
    - List of all King County Nurses Association Committees and Chairs, 1983-1985 (Box-folder 5/14)
  - COMMUNICATION/POLITICAL AWARENESS COMMITTEE, 1975-1985; SUBGROUP 5 (Box-folder 5/15-20)
    Contains records related to political advocacy surrounding issues relevant to nursing and health care.
    - Legislation and Puget Sound Health Systems Agency, 1975-1983 (Box-folder 5/15)
    - King County Health Planning Council and Health Systems Agency, 1977-1980 (Box-folder 5/16)
    - Communications/Political Awareness: King County Health Planning Council Candidate Interviews, 1978-1979 (Box-folder 5/17)
    - Communication/Political Awareness Committee Correspondence, 1978-1985 (Box-folder 5/18)
    - Communication/Political Awareness Committee Minutes, 1979-1985 (Box-folder 5/19)
    - Communication/Political Awareness Testimonies, 1980 (Box-folder 5/20)
  - ETHNIC MINORITY AFFAIRS COMMITTEE, 1982-1986; SUBGROUP 6 (Box-folder 5/21)
    Contains meeting minutes of the committee which advocated for nurses belonging to ethnic minority groups as well as the health care needs of individuals from these communities.
    - Ethnic Minority Affairs Committee Meeting Minutes, 1982-1986 (Box-folder 5/21)
  - EXCELLENCE IN NURSING PRACTICE AWARDS COMMITTEE, 1979-1986; SUBGROUP 7 (Box-folder 5/22-30)
    - Minutes and Committee Member Correspondence, 1981-1986 (Box-folder 5/22)
    - Awardee Nomination and Selection Materials, 1979 (Box-folder 5/23)
    - Awardee Nomination and Selection Materials, 1980 (Box-folder 5/24)
    - Awardee Nomination and Selection Materials, 1981 (Box-folder 5/25)
    - Awardee Nomination and Selection Materials, 1982 (Box-folder 5/26)
    - Awardee Nomination and Selection Materials, 1983 (Box-folder 5/27)
    - Awardee Nomination and Selection Materials, 1984 (Box-folder 5/28)
    - Awardee Nomination and Selection Materials, 1985 (Box-folder 5/29)
    - Awardee Nomination and Selection Materials, 1986 (Box-folder 5/30)
  - FINANCE COMMITTEE, 1974-1987; SUBGROUP 8 (Box-folder 5/31-37)
    Contains records related to the KCNA annual budget as well as committee correspondence and meeting minutes.
    - Correspondence, 1974-1985 (Box-folder 5/31)
    - Budget Reports and Policy Documentation, 1975-1987 (Box-folder 5/32)
    - Meeting Minutes, 1976 May-1986 January (Box-folder 5/33)
    - Finance Committee and Board of Directors 1981-82 Budget Request Worksheets, 1981-1983 (Box-folder 5/34)
    - "Taking Budgeting from Abstract to Reality" Workshop, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 5/35)
    - Finance Committee Budget Forms, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 5/36)
    - Pending 1985-86 Budget Information/Requests, 1984-1986 (Box-folder 5/37)
  - MEMBERSHIP COMMITTEE, 1972-1987; SUBGROUP 9 (Box-folder 5/38-41)
    Contains records related to new member recruitment and onboarding.
    - New Member Recruitment, 1972-1986 (Box-folder 5/38)
    - Correspondence, 1978-1986 (Box-folder 5/39)
    - Monthly Welcome Letters, 1978-1987 (Box-folder 5/40)
    - Meeting Minutes, 1979 February-1986 January (Box-folder 5/41)
  - NOMINATION COMMITTEE, 1977-1987; SUBGROUP 10 (Box-folder 6/1-12)
    Contains records related to board member, officer, nomination committee members, and Washington State Nurses Association delegate nominations and elections.
    - Meeting Minutes and Correspondence, 1977 November-1986 April (Box-folder 6/1)
    - 1979 Election Materials, 1978-1979 (Box-folder 6/2)
    - Tally Sheets, 1978-1980 (Box-folder 6/3)
    - 1980 Election Materials (Box-folder 6/4)
    - 1981 Election Materials, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 6/5)
    - Washington State Convention Delegate Process - Reference Material, 1981 (Box-folder 6/6)
    - 1982 Election Materials (Box-folder 6/7)
    - 1983 Election Materials (Box-folder 6/8)
    - 1984 Election Materials, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 6/9)
    - 1985 Election Materials (Box-folder 6/10)
    - 1986 Election Materials, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 6/11)
    - 1987 Election Materials, 1986-1987 (Box-folder 6/12)
  - NURSE OF THE YEAR AWARD COMMITTEE, 1978-1985; SUBGROUP 11 (Box-folder 6/13-20)
    Contains records related to awardee nominations and selection.
    - 1978 Nurse of the Year (Box-folder 6/13)
    - 1979-80 Nurse of the Year, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 6/14)
    - 1981 Nurse of the Year (Box-folder 6/15)
    - 1982 Nurse of the Year, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 6/16)
    - 1983 Nurse of the Year, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 6/17)